Aubrey Camille Soliman

I am a PHP programmer with 3+ years of commercial experience. I have spear-headed multiple related project feature release. I like to read about the latest technologies and current popular frameworks during my spare time. Currently I am learning AngularJS, C#, ASP .NET, Visual Basic and SQL Management Studio.

EDUCATION

Mapua University (Philippines)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology. Major in SAS Business Analytics.

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

WEB TECHNOLOGIES

PHP, Linux, Apache, JSON/API, Bootstrap, HTML5/JavaScript/CSS, ASP.NET MVC, AngularJS

DATABASES

MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server

TOOLS/LIBRARIES

PHP Storm, Git, Redmine, Backlog, Ganglia, ReShaper, Visual Studio 2012

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MVP Studio (New Zealand)

Software Development Intern

Oct 2017 - Present

Currently working on the on-boarding task.

- ASP .NET MVC, C#, AngularJS, HTML/JavaScript/AJAX/CSS/jQuery and SQL Server
- List all the tasks you have done here.

ImpactNPO (New Zealand)

Website Developer (Volunteer)

Sep 2017 (2-Day Event)

Website development made during hackathon event led by ImpactNPO for client She# (https://www.shesharp.co.nz/).

I have created two of the pages (About Our Team and Event) using Wordpress.

Aiming Global Services Inc. (Philippines)

Development Staff

Mar 2017 - Apr 2017

Project: Eagle Fantasy Golf

Localization of language from Chinese to English using Unity 3D

KLab Cyscorpions (Philippines)

Software Engineer

Oct 2013 - Feb 2017

Projects: Eternal Uprising and Lord of the Dragons

- PHP (CakePHP Framework), MySQL, Linux, Apache, MVC, HTML/JavaScript /CSS(Bootstrap/
- Developed feature releases with MVC design pattern using DietCake Framework (optimized CakePHP framework)

- Main Developer in multiple API release and continuous CMS update
- User data management (migration, maintenance, data update and backup)
- Creation of API, Database Schema Design and Logic Specifications
- Development environment (LOCAL → STAGING → PRODUCTION)
- Redmine Issue Management (Test if bug is occurring → assign it to developers or fix it myself → re-test if bug is still occurring)
- Investigation of issues sent by a player and customer support via email
- Monitoring of Amazon Web Services (AWS) instance using Ganglia

INTERESTS

- Trying out other PHP frameworks such as Laravel and Silverstripe.
- A very active person who loves trying out new things and is always up for any challenge.
- Loves travelling a lot, learning other cultures, tasting different kind of foods and taking photographs.

REFEREES

Available on request